This nanodegree program requires you to complete five different projects.
此纳米级程序要求您完成五个不同的项目
The first project is the route planner project,,
第一个项目是路线规划师项目
in which you'll build a route planner to find a route between
在此期间 您将构建路线规划程序以在
any two points in a real city using data from the OpenStreetMap Project.
使用 OpenStreetMap 项目的数据 在真实城市中的任何两个点
The second project is the system monitor project,
第二个项目是系统监控项目
in which you'll implement your own version of the top program that identifies
您将在其中实施您自己的顶级程序版本 以标识
variables relevant to your system and prints out
与系统相关的变量并打印出
information about all the different processes running on your computer.
有关计算机上运行的所有不同进程的信息
The third project is the garbage collector project,
第三个项目是垃圾收集器项目
in which you'll build your own version of smart pointers,
你将会建立自己的智能指针版本
a way to keep track of dynamically allocated memory and prevent memory leaks.
跟踪动态分配的内存并防止内存泄漏
The fourth project is a traffic simulation.
第四个项目是交通模拟
In this project, you'll use
在这个项目中 你会使用
concurrent multi-threaded programming to organize traffic flow through a city.
同时进行多线程编程以组织流量流经城市
Each vehicle will run on its own thread,
每辆车都在自己的线上运行
and you'll use thread synchronization and
然后你就会使用线程同步
communication to help the vehicles navigate intersections,
沟通 帮助车辆浏览路口
and help traffic flow smoothly through the city.
并帮助交通顺利通过城市
The final project of this nanodegree program is the Capstone project.
这个纳米级项目的最终项目是 Capstone 项目
In this project, you'll build your own C++ application using
在此项目中 您将使用以下项构建自己的 C++ 应用程序 :
many of the different skills and techniques that
很多不同的技能和技巧
you've learned as part of this nanodegree program.
你已经学会了这个纳米级的计划